{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "3 * 5 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "15",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "7", "6", "9" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 * 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "6", "12", "7" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "5 * 6 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "30",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "20", "22", "25" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "6 * 3 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "18",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "4", "9", "12" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "7 * 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "63",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "56", "72", "81" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "8 * 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "32",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "24", "30", "35" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "9 * 3 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "27",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "24", "30", "25" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "10 * 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "20",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "12", "15", "18" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "11 * 7 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "77",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "66", "84", "92" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "12 * 8 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "96",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "84", "108", "120" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "13 * 5 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "65",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "52", "70", "78" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "14 * 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "56",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "48", "60", "72" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "15 * 9 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "135",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "120", "150", "162" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "16 * 3 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "48",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "36", "42", "54" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "17 * 6 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "102",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "84", "120", "136" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "18 * 2 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "36",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "24", "30", "40" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "19 * 4 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "76",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "64", "80", "92" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "20 * 7 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "140",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "120", "150", "160" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "21 * 3 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "63",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "54", "72", "81" ]
    },
    {
      "question": "22 * 8 = ?",
      "correctAnswer": "176",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "154", "192", "208" ]
    }
  ]
}